broadband-finder.co.uk 2014-09-16

# Privacy Policy | Broadband Finder

The following privacy statement explains our policy regarding the personal information we collect about you.

#### General privacy policy

This policy covers Broadband Finder's use of personal information that is collected when a user visits our website. The policy also covers other issues relating to personal privacy and how Broadband Finder respects your privacy. Broadband Finder will occasionally ask you for personal information so that we can provide you with a better service or use of tools on our site. Such services/tools include our newsletter, reminder service, broadband comparison and broadband finder. This personal information is solely used to provide you with the service that you requested and is never sold or shared with any third party.

#### Visitor information

With every visit to our site, we will either set or update a cookie on your system. This is just a small text file that will enable us to track where you came from and how useful you found our site. The information that we gather from cookies can not be used to identify you and cannot be used for any sort of illegal activity. The information that cookies give us allow us to provide a better service to our users and provide certain users will specific information that relates to their searching patterns. Once again this information cannot be used to identify you and will never be shared with any third party.

#### Storage of personal information

Occasionally some of the tools available on our website will require you submit personal information to us, such as our newsletter or reminder service. We will always inform you when we collect this information and will only use this to provide you with the service that you requested. All of the personal information we collect is stored on our database servers and every effort is made to make sure that our servers remain secure. We will ensure that all personal information supplied is held securely, in accordance with the Data Protection Act of 1998.

#### Your rights

You have the right to see the personal information we have stored about you upon request. If the information is inaccurate, incomplete or irrelevant, you have the right to request that the information be corrected or deleted.

#### External links

Our website contains links to other external sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware that when they leave our site they should read the privacy policy of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies just to information collected by our website.

#### Policy Changes

By using our website you agree to accept this privacy policy and are aware that our policy may change with time. Any changes to this policy will appear on this web page.

#### Website operated by

This website is operated by UK Web Media LTD, and UK Web Media is a registered company in England & Wales No. 04388827. Registered Address: UK Web Media Unit 8 The Fairground Industrial Estate, Weyhill, Hampshire, SP11 0QN http://www.ukwebmedia.com

Sky TV prices will increase on 1 September. In accordance with their standard terms, your Sky TV package may rise by up to 10% in a minimum contract term.
